{
    "id": "6c4b26e070ae488f82f3a0686a5e0f13",
    "title": "Grammar And Vocabulary Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The travellers rested under a …………………….. of trees.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "choir",
                "clump",
                "clan"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "51011b4ec55e49e285861a3847fc9000"
        },
        {
            "question": "While taking a stroll in my garden, I was attacked by a ………………………… of bees.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "swarm",
                "group",
                "cluster"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b7e3c4996beb4c1183f9b0f1efe6c198"
        },
        {
            "question": "What will you do if you find an abandoned ………………………….. of kittens?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "troupe",
                "litter",
                "band"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c3bbbc70b3a64131a30e9649e40828df"
        },
        {
            "question": "Each of these novels ……………………… worth reading.",
            "description": "Use a singular verb after each.",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b4f8f162790c4194b7e35bdb7529d34e"
        },
        {
            "question": "The children were accompanied …………………….. their mother.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "by",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "517f659041da4351986f45cb74605a65"
        },
        {
            "question": "I found ……………………….. empty bottle floating on the water.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "an",
                "a"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "093e5cd22f2748f0b2b83fe53e9c259f"
        },
        {
            "question": "He, as well as I, ……………………….. great interest in politics.",
            "description": "When we connect two nouns with as well as, the verb agrees with the former. ",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "has"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ea2b9912a31442ae946ead7cf8cdf3d6"
        },
        {
            "question": "The minister unlike his sons ……………………… honest.",
            "description": "Here the subject is the singular noun minister.",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5f5f856745b241ebb401c4014da30af5"
        },
        {
            "question": "Close the door. Change into passive",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Door be closed.",
                "Be the door closed.",
                "Let the door be closed."
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "05c7af6c9ceb4a7fa933a95b821aa611"
        },
        {
            "question": "Either you or your brother ……………………….. to clean the room.",
            "description": "When two singular nouns are connected with either/or, the verb agrees with the latter.",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "has"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4cc47ab62fe84341afc4d055c00f8c4e"
        },
        {
            "question": "Neither my brother nor my sisters ……………………. married.",
            "description": "When two singular nouns are connected with either/or, the verb agrees with the latter.",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4905434f602046bf8a91a003f6704c88"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the female of fox …………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Foxen",
                "Foxess",
                "Vixen"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "2abbe23c748e495a8aff0f4020e03409"
        }
    ]
}